

Muhammad Ibrahim

Nationality: Pakistani (+92) 3107483892 **Date of birth:** 15/05/1997

Gender: Male **☑ Email address:** <u>Ibrahimzooq7744049@gmail.com</u>

• Address: H# 193 Gulraiz Town Basti Shore Kot M.A Jinnah Road Chowk Kumhara H# 193 Gulraiz Town Basti Shore Kot M.A Jinnah Road Chowk Kumhara, 60000 Multan (Pakistan)

ABOUT ME

Senior Web Developer specializing in front-end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP, CSS, MySQL WordPress. Strong background in project management and customer relations

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web developer

Comtech [29/12/2018 - 11/10/2019]

City: Multan **Country:** Pakistan

☑ Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences. ☑ Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow. ☑ Work with senior developers to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients. ☑ Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front-end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code. ☑ Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability

IT-Instructor

MNSUET Multan [18/12/2019 - 16/06/2020]

City: Multan

Country: Pakistan

Still, I am working as an IT Instructor at MNS University of Engineering & Technology III I experienced here how we manage our duties.

Academic support officer

MNSUET Multan [05/11/2020 - 30/06/2021]

City: Multan **Country:** Pakistan

Research managers

Office of Research Innovation and Commercialization (ORIC) [06/10/2011 - 29/06/2022]

City: Multan **Country:** Pakistan

To make research top precedence among faculty members of the University of Multan, the Office of Research Innovation and Commercialization (ORIC) is established that aims to promote and enhance research activities and help them to commercialize and industrialize. ORIC provides a complete platform to the researchers and augment's their research skills from a working bench to a furnished product. ORIC also provides services related to research and development, innovation, industrialization, commercialization, collaborations, seminars, workshops, submission and approval of research projects

In-Charge ORIC
Dr. Ali Hassan
Ph.D. Chemical Engineering

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor's in Computer Science

Muhammad Nawaz Sharif University of Engineering & Technology, MNSUET [2018 - 2022]

Address: QasimPur Colony, BCG Chowk, Multan, Punjab, Pakistan, 60000 Multan (Pakistan)

https://mnsuet.edu.pk/

Final grade: A

Thesis: Face Detection Based Attendance & Covid-19 Vaccine Verification System

- Digital Computer Design Fundamentals
- Object Oriented Programming
- Data Structures
- Software Engineering and Project Management
- Database Systems
- Computer Graphics
- Computer Logic Design and Computer Organization

FSC

Board of Intermediate and Secondary Education, Dera Ghazi Khan [2016 – 2018]

Address: 3M6H+8W9, Board Rd, D G Khan, Dera Ghazi Khan, Punjab, 32260 Dera Ghazi Khan (Pakistan)

https://www.bisedgkhan.edu.pk/

Final grade: 1st Division

Matric

Board of Intermediate and Secondary Education, Dera Ghazi Khan [2013 – 2015]

Address: 3M6H+8W9, Board Rd, D G Khan, Dera Ghazi Khan, Punjab, 32260 Dera Ghazi Khan (Pakistan)

https://www.bisedgkhan.edu.pk/

Final grade: 1st Division

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Urdu

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Project management / WordPress / 🖫 Strong decision maker / Complex problem solver / Creative design / 🖺 PHP Backend Developer / Front-end Developer / Service-focused / Microsoft Powerpoint / Mircosoft Word / Computer Literate / Computer Application / Social Media / web developers / web designer

RECOMMENDATIONS

Head Of Department Computer Science

Name: Dr. Kashif Ali

Phone number: (+92) 3026329787 Email: kashifali 381@yahoo.com

Head Of Department Computer Science

Head of Department

Name: Engr. Dr. Muhammad Shahzad Email: dr.shehzad@mnsuet.edu.pk

Head of Department Electrical Engineering & Technology